I'm gonna give it a little guess what
Ryan sent us we're live oh we are live
all right junkyard love podcast my
brother yeah the junk yard love punk ass
that's crazy I thought that I was gonna
have some crazy cool like just artistic
name like extension of junkyard love cuz
I thought of that a while ago but I
don't know joke I love podcast has been
kind of sticking no yeah I love it
I mean it's it just makes me think of
you know it's a lot of things that you
want to talk about that are you know
just random stuff you know just a
junkyard of stuff yeah a junkyard
you know another man's junk is someone
else's treasure yeah this one's a yard
of treasure Lee love welcome to the yard
of tress really love like I feel like
this is like if you were introducing
some sort of like well I think I should
say that the thickening of my pot goes
like welcome to the yard of treasure
lilo ladies and gentlemen where we have
but then that would be like of you know
those old radio shows back in the day
where it's like the late-night radio hey
baby
what do you want to talk about yeah
what's your what was that one welcome
it's just somehow junk out love is
sexting it ya know love is now a sexual
podcast by the way the only talk about
sex
yeah and I you got the wrong person for
that not even know he's a virgin yes yes
no actually so Ryan Santos my friend
yeah welcome everybody Ryan Santos this
has been a good friend of mine for quite
some time we worked together at a tuxedo
rental place back when I was in high
school he's a few years ahead of me but
I was in high school work to admit a
taxi no rental place in the mall mister
formal tuxedos you can then he had some
adventures and I just wanted I had to
have around in the podcast just because
he's been one of the more positive
influential friends of my life just like
always to regardless the crazy [__]
we've been through
he's just been like I mean don't you
have to keep smiling tattooed on your
wrist yeah I do and I just want to say
thank you in person thank you for that
Jake I mean I really appreciate it I
really appreciate you asking me to be on
this show you know and yeah it's been an
honor to be your really good friend I
mean always I've never not that about
you make sure you're doing all right and
man our little adventures when we first
became friends have been insane and yeah
you know obviously I'm here for a reason
and it's been awesome thanks man yeah
I'm glad to have you I'm glad I think
you know it's dorky and simple as it
sounds I'm glad for the world to meet
you I don't really know where this
podcast is gonna go like I don't you
know like like I want as many people to
listen to it as as they think is
valuable at don't worry buddy listen to
it just because they know who I am or
know my DJ world whatever I just want
people to listen to it with value so I
like all the guests that I have on here
is just like who is someone who like
it's valuable every time talk to him and
you're just deep definitely fit that
category so oh for sure that's how I
feel about you man every time we get
together we just like just talk for
hours yeah but now that we're on here
I'm just like oh my gosh what are we
even talk about right this is right to
talk about now because we talked about
it we talked about some crazy things I
know I think I think that I mean this
will be among the first the first 20
episodes I have quite a few stacking up
now just be among the first 20 but I
think after a while after it becomes
very good thing people understand like
okay like you know Jake and his friends
and in the people around him are just
like they talk about crazy stuff
sometimes like they're not crazy they're
just they just love until someone crazy
stuff you know so dude if we if this
somehow this whole conversation have we
talked about aliens like we untie aliens
get into them I [__] love that stuff
if you watch the on
they have on Netflix like the Bob Lazar
like area 51
oh I started like the first 10 minutes
of it but it was one of those I put it
on and I fell asleep the same day oh man
it looks really good yeah I don't know a
ton about it I would say I have friends
who have watched it and then he was on
like the general Ogun podcast and stuff
so I know I don't know a ton about it
but essentially I think it's he worked
in area 51 for a little bit and then he
like was a whistleblower like something
like a over there 51 here's what I saw
but who hasn't though and all those like
I used to work at area 51 I'm like how
did you become out and do this interview
then you could more data you're doing
they don't come after you and your
family nope okay just no oh yeah you're
good so yeah so something about this
headphone like I don't know if this
little headphone thing that I got from
Amazon is like it doesn't support very
much so if I do too much movement it's
like no I'm scared power mode okay like
protective over my chest Amazon man
that's another one you notice that their
reviews on Amazon are just like you
can't try something we used to go to to
to to trust but now we know it's all
fake it's written for other [__] well
yeah that's what happens when you get
really popular I mean not really popular
but like the amount of people using or
buying from your like store or whatever
it gets stupid after that it's like oh
we got you we hooked you in guess why
right now we can sell whatever the [__]
we want
you know we're gonna tell you what you
want no yeah that's what I don't like
either it's like you may all also like
these items right it's like yeah like
you you could have like them but you're
fine without knowing they exist how
about that yeah like you but have you
okay so you've you've more than reason I
mean you weren't super in the social
mean I don't feel like but you've had
social media if like as long as I have
like we've both we've had our shirtless
pictures together on social media oh
we've shared this oh yeah I mean every
year that I for some reason I the reason
why I kept sharing is because it came up
like Oh memories you know like it's such
a great time in our life that was such a
funny day to like
we have this photo everybody just
listening we have this photo that when
we worked in mr. formal like we were
both working out and we like just fresh
bro Me's and we would stand in like in
the place where like you go to get
married for your wedding and we were
just like peace symbols up in the shirt
or in the mirror Sheila's both of us
have a typical like 2001-2009 or
something to that I was wearing
Hollister pants with holes in them for
sure like like they were fresh off the
press fresh holes freshly made in the
factory yeah and you had a way you were
still in high school right yeah yeah and
yeah that big ass tattoo oh yeah no yeah
I was like 17 when I got my first so my
exact right side that was my first how
did that okay hold on now that I really
think about it how did that even go down
like yeah okay but my my life is just
different
I I my tattoo artist this was like so
long ago but my tattoo artist was like
literally a lady who had changed my
diapers like my family grew up like a
tattoo family okay and so they would
really have to hat to parties as I was
growing up and so when I was younger I I
remember getting all 10 of my nails
tattooed at some point and that was
something like cool badass thing wait
wait you you got yeah nails you can get
your nails tattooed yeah it's hot it's
warm uh-huh yeah but it's it doesn't
cause pain like it's more just kind of
sketchy yeah but I don't know exactly
how how they do it I remember how the
person did it but I think she's a
regular around needles but I got that
one other kid so I thought that was
super cool and then I was like no I
don't want a to is like it's too
permanent I don't want it yeah and then
I got to this point where I was at this
very like rubella I mean one of the very
rebellious stages of my young life and I
was like how do you want to you and so
yeah when it was a family friend but
she's a very like she's a good tattoo
artist that's all knowledge it but yeah
my whole right side and you can imagine
being like a 16 year old dude with ABS
like who has a tattoo on his right side
oh yeah it's like such a turd I was such
a turd it turned into do you girls want
to see me with my shirt off because
you're going to as I'm driving by yeah
anywhere I'm going I'm just if you're
willing to take your shirt off for a
photo and
tuxedo place after hours with your bro I
think you're willing to take your shirt
off anywhere that's the thing
yeah like the things you do like oh oh
there's a customer like there's to be
during hours imagine if you walk into
any place you're going into a bakery and
I come to get some donuts and you're
like excuse me hello
and you clients the background and the
employees are just taking shirts
oh my gosh
oh my how many stupid things have we
done that please that's the thing we've
done a lot of stupid place okay what
what do you think is the what's the cool
story you can think of from working at
mr. Foreman when we were in high school
so I okay the wait so baseline this is
mr. formal in the mall at the Kelso mall
tourism all fairly dead at times but
like it was probably the one tuxedo
rental place if you go to prom or you're
having a wedding yeah where you go in
town from art generally oh yeah for sure
they had that place where we worked at
and then then they have like the rents
and events mmm that mean you could get
tuxedos too but I never heard anyone go
in there unless you know where was like
negative stuff about them I don't know
if that was like just because I had to
do with her job well we were I mean come
on dude we're the best yeah we and then
they only had like limited [__] to my
hair do you want to look like you just
got done doing an orchestra yeah the
coat-tails
that's funny we're like they're like
yeah well we're gonna special events
events and were like yeah if you want to
look like a [__] idiot who just talk
people out of it we don't even know
anything about that's what the tattoo is
on a stump that's what it is if you're
listening right now that's you can quote
me on that it says that but anyways yeah
the craziest thing that has ever
happened at mr. formal I think it was
when I smoked weed in the bathroom we
did that no I did that too we would but
that was after hours I did during the
day during hours I feel like I probably
participated in that you know it like
it's not something I'm like
you know it's a laughable moment now you
know and I feel like it seems so insane
you know saying that we like we would
smoke weed or something like yeah we're
working like I think just in our world
the world that we grew up in like we I
really generally wouldn't say that we're
bad people bad kids bad like you know we
had it together like I was I was and you
were both like higher up and in
commissions in the company like we did
well we showed up to our job on time I
think for sure it's so funny thinking
back about like the little [__] stuff we
did you know yeah but we were able to
kind of keep it afloat like I'm not
saying I'm no advocate for smoking weed
and the bathrooms are trying to work but
it is so funny that the the importance
of I feel like we've been such good
friends for so long but I think it's
because we really went out of our way
back in the day like even much formal
times like hang out and like build a
connection like oh yeah we were friends
like we didn't have to be friends we we
were from different worlds but like we
hung out outside of work we have enough
that smoking weed in the bathroom is is
the best way to form a connection with
the co-workers but yeah hell if that's
what you got yeah I mean like there's
not much to do and longview Kelso or
just even in Cal's County area and the
time you know there is now I mean things
that are available but back then we just
had to make our own fun and I think
that's exactly what we did and you know
like you said we didn't have to be
friends but you know definitely it's
like it's hard to be good for us with
your coworkers because the things that
you can bring into like like imagine if
we didn't hit it off or something work
it was like then we would have to go to
work yeah yeah oh my god dude you
[__] so I don't worry you all right
you know i mean i think i think that we
all did I mean even with our bosses like
we you know it's work but we all did
based off of our personalities based off
of like who we were and like just like
you we didn't all go into it saying
we're all the same we're all very
different oh yeah our boss is like we
would joke around with with our bosses
you know oh yeah we would be very very
different people like listen different
music different hairstyles different
clothes whatever
yeah but we I feel like just our
personalities we go into work and say
how do I make this fun
yeah like no you can't always smoke weed
with your with your manager oh yeah chef
what thank you yeah yeah I think it is
important for everyone to like really
realize your your role like I could dude
it doesn't matter just cause you're not
a manager at a store like if you're an
employee if you're new employee old
employee you kind of got a job man like
remember like yeah you're spending your
time there but everybody you're around
is spending their time to like yeah you
could make you your job fun you can go a
little bit extra you can pay 12 bucks on
Wednesday and bring some doughnuts
whatever I'm like I think that we did a
good job
I'm mr. formal of finding our fun fun
and dude we were we were good I felt
like yeah it really sucks is London
right doesn't matter who was walking up
or like you need a tux yeah we're gonna
give it to you federal fetch it we were
not competitive if you think about it a
lot of like on TV shows or other places
they're like this they're competitive
with each other oh yeah be definitely a
Salesman yeah we weren't we weren't
super competitive with each other
against each other like we were like
loop and each other and they're like oh
how much commissioner gee oh hell yeah
oh yeah this month yeah exactly it
wasn't super against each other it was
like how can we all do super good yeah
and I think I start killed it oh yeah
it's like you said but when we're
whenever we're making a sale it's not
like that other like if I was making a
sale it's not like you were like sitting
in the back just sitting there or
whatever you would actually come out and
help me like yeah definitely if it's a
party or something you would come out
and help me nice money like oh hey what
would you like you know and even though
that I got the Commission it's like you
were still there yeah it's the same way
yeah and you know what's funny is it's
back then you know affect the world now
were always like oh we'll make sure I
get my credit or like even down to
[__] like oh hey I handed you my
phone to take a photo and you make sure
like a photo credit goes to whatever
yeah everybody wants credit for
everything and like I feel like back
then we did a very good job of just I
know that you're here to help me when I
need it so I'm here to help you like
even if here to help you means I'm
working every day like more it seems
like whatever like I just know that
you're gonna be there for me like
there's no credit there's no like it's
Mike we're like well hey I'm which the
mission do I get ya know ya know we
about that like yeah exactly I don't
think we ever you owe me this or
whatever that never happened like I
really don't think we ever even had I
mean maybe there was some stuff with
other people that like we weren't aware
of or something I don't know but but I
don't know I feel like we did a very
good job because we had our other we had
other co-workers who we got along with
really well to you yeah hey Kip Kip yeah
that sucks for him right now
yeah I don't want it I don't know if I
want to dive into that I mean we can but
let's just say that he is in other
places at other times and he did
something really stupid yeah never
thought that would you know why when
someone showed me that I was like yeah
yes and I were what we were like no yes
not a real thing but not until I saw it
on TV
right that's [__] weird man I weren't
do did great he's my guy yeah one of the
like crazy intelligent people that you
and me he just he just knew what he
wanted he knew how to get it diabla but
now it all makes sense really good
you're good at something until you get
calm until you're too good at it yeah
you're a professional at it and you got
to keep doing what you got to do to be a
professional but I didn't think you'd
take it to the fashion bandit that was
[__] hilarious
oh man I still like mine blog about that
like what is it like well me too that'd
be Hillier
dang like I didn't I don't even realize
I was addressing up like if you like if
you were robbing some stores oh my oh
it's okay if you were if you were
robbing stuff and like the only thing
you can come up with by the way is
dressing up you just look at hellofresh
like it's like what do you look like how
does he look so good officer he was
dressing he he was dressed to the nines
but he was wearing women's clothing but
it looked [__] good though like yeah
what was he wearing honestly he was
wearing a red dress with the red high
heels it's so good though I just want to
write that down
make sure they add him his eyes were so
kind his eyes are so kind but what he
was asking for was very [__]
demanding and dangerous he seemed to
really want my money I don't care but
those shoes did we're not supposed to
come out until next year but he somehow
he had can we know that somehow he had
the the next season shoes however he got
those if I officer if you can let me
know I really want to get those they're
not even out yet oh my gosh okay so I do
want to like just because we're talk
about the mr. formal thing I want to
share this story oh I want I want to let
you tell it but the story of when we
first smoked weed together we had worked
maybe even one shift together is me you
and a lot of oh yeah in we get on it
Zack Johnson right yeah yeah and this is
super strange I gotta figure out what's
gonna power thing but yeah so this is
this is a story so the reason why I want
to share the story so this cemetery that
this situation took place this is I go
this is Mike one of my favorite
meditation city lookout spots I go here
like once a week at least like late at
night like recently mmm yeah yeah the
Mount bring named graveyard up there
yeah top yeah I go there probably once a
week like the meditate up top there mmm
but it's cool going there like because
sometimes I'll remember that random
memory of that night and I'll just do it
I'll just like it so giggle Bowl like
I'll just laugh so hard yeah so so share
that memory so this was we had to work
together what four or five times if at
one of the homes man yeah probably it's
like we've been working for like two
week I've been working maybe two weeks
at this job at mr. formal but finally we
became friends good enough friends
because we had that mutual friend that
got me the job Zach right and so we all
smoked right after in the car and then
we went up to what was it Mountain
brainian oh yeah yeah so we went up top
oh my god this is so funny it's such a
simple it's produces smoke weed up there
Oh everybody weed up there before yeah
but your reaction was priceless
so we get up top and mind you this spot
you when you get up top of this hill
this like graveyard is like one huge
hill so when you get up top you could
see a long view you can see Kelso you
can even see all the way over to the
rainier bridge oh it's amazing so we
went up there I haven't been up there in
years it's been years I love to get you
stoned and pick you up there already got
freaking almost arrested up there for
that yeah not anymore
but so we go there we smoked checking
out this awesome view and we're starting
to leave and then there's roads in
between the graveyards mind you so it's
like drive all over yeah it's like
gravel so it's it's pathways right you
know it's it is gravel pathway so you
can drive on like it's Rayleigh for norm
but on your left and your right like
just a few feet is like literally
tombstones like you're you're driving
in-between tombstones which is like that
they made it that way yeah it's pretty
intense like it's not like you park your
over here and then you walk into the guy
ride it's like you're the this is a
square block radius sort of situation if
the tombstones being the buildings yeah
so driving down one of the pathways and
all of a sudden we just means act just
here and the in the back of the car guys
what the [__] are you doing what are you
guys doing that you guys are driving
over the graveyard like where you guys
are driving over the tombs and we just
start busting up like dude calm down
we're just negative pathway and mind you
he you were at the time 16 and I think
16 17 and we were 20 21 and so we're
kind of almost we were just laughing
around like dude this kid is freaking
out dude I was like okay okay okay so to
me to me I genuinely thought so I was
like I probably like talked to that but
I had only been smoking since I was like
four a year
yeah like and so I probably talked it
out but I was like probably super high I
was in the backseat of like these two
dudes who I think are the coolest
[__] dudes ever yeah like we smoked
you out to do the lot on price
to town a weed I was probably just
trying to hang equally with him like
that's probably like not saying only a
single hit but as we're driving like I'm
looking forward I'm sitting in the
backseat like looking through their
console in the mind you this is a very
it wasn't a big car it was like he could
see the other like this course it's like
an eclipse or something like it
it was his like read some it was a red
car or that like you can barely see out
of the sides in the back anyways like
it's a pretty close so you don't see in
the front yeah really
and I remember you're just like because
even sitting in the front it's like hard
to see for some reason over the hood
kind of thing yeah you can only kind of
see what directly what the headlights
are piercing on the other thing goes
kind of later at night yeah it was kind
of late it was so kind of like light out
but just enough for ya yeah okay because
I generally thought so I look forward I
was thinking of some sort of crazy I
thought and then I look forward and I'm
a hundred percent convinced we are form
head falling we are mobbing over people
scribes like me I'm in the backseat
holding on because I'm so high I was
like I thought that we were just Zack
was like [__] these grades yeah [__]
these people under here [__] their
corpses like yeah are disrespecting like
I yeah for some reason that was it was
such a surefire thing to me I remember
it so vividly like because I was like
these guys are so cool and I turned
around and I look out the front
windshield and to me we're driving
through graves
yeah and so I'm like this is not right I
will not have a part of this what the
[__] you guys I remember that it was so
funny because you guys like I freaked
out and then you guys like didn't say
anything and then you like you let me
like chill and then you said something
like dude we're fine we're on the
pathway it was this sobering moment of
me looking forward and it's like freaked
out were like I was like what do I will
not be a part I was not raised like I
don't know you got this is not OK to me
like but it was awkward our work
relationship would have been if you
think that was like you're like well
this is what we do would you ever grace
yeah yeah if we never said anything it's
like if you [__] say anything about
us driving over those graveyards yeah
like most people have weird secrets but
you're like we have a spot for you over
there on Thursday nights after work Oh
was a great memory yes so that was I
mean that really broke into like we were
hanging out like all the time oh right
after that yeah after that Fiasco of
being high and not knowing what the hell
we were doing is yeah even like though
that we were I was 20 or 21 I can't
remember I think I was 20 because I
can't go to bars yet but even then I
still look at myself as a kid right not
knowing and just you know going to work
smoking weed all day and not caring
about it I mean we we really did you
know I don't want to be naive about like
Corning yourself into a good corner but
like we really weren't like we were bad
people yeah we weren't like it's you
know people in our world we just live
very different lives like we we had it
together like you and I like our store
particularly like in that moment we were
like very good like we had high-end
sales we showed up on time each other
out we enjoy each other's company like
our manager was happy like we did good
at our jobs we were kind of like turds
you know no I definitely I was in high
school I had good grades like I like all
these things that we talked about doing
like we had it together it's just a
different life than other people it is
but I think yeah I think there's a lot
of other kids along other little
knucklehead it's a lot of little [__]
right now or here in this or somehow me
might be hearing this one day that like
I'm the same boat oh it's just a
never-ending cycle of news kids going
through the same things that we are I
mean it's probably you know their
situations are totally different but at
the same time the immoralist story is
that hey we've done what you've done you
know yeah and we know it you're not the
first ones yeah which is sad because
everyone's done everything you know like
we were talking about earlier like
everyone's written that song before a
variation of that song and you know when
it comes to doing stupid [__] people
have done it before and you know you're
not alone you know just be safe people
be safe yeah man I really think like you
know it sounds dorky we live in a world
where you know that's huge thing I've
had to I've had to concur with this
podcast like already is talking about
drugs talking about druggie is talking
about
she thought it was stupid like as much
as that makes everybody very
uncomfortable as much as that's like
that's not what you do online that's
there forever it's like it really
happened and if I'm gonna lie about it
or you're gonna lie about it or or
whoever's going to not be honest about
what actually happened their life that's
one less thing that a young kid who has
experienced the same [__] or my
experience the same [__] now has nothing
to look up to like mm-hmm
like like kids need to know that like
the stuff that they're doing like it's
not okay like you're a turd but like
it's also it is okay yeah like like not
not giving people permission to go out
and do drugs but letting kids know that
that hey you're you're gonna see that
thing and you're gonna say it's stupid
like yeah do what you need to do be it
be as smart as you are right now
experience what you need to experience
but like it's gonna be okay if you just
you know yeah and what's hard about that
like you know is trying to tell them hey
if you're gonna do it be safe you know
how we were just talking about that we
were smoking and driving and right of
course so we're gonna no place you're
not supposed to smoke that's all bad and
I will not lie about that you know
that's all bad but at the same time
those are the memories I would never
take that like those are the things that
oh my gosh that was so funny at the time
dangerous whatever whatever you want to
call that not good but oh my gosh yeah I
love talking about that every time we
easily see yeah okay graveyard dude yeah
we always remember that [__] it's so fun
to me because it was just like it's such
a wonderful first time to like hang out
and me and like like it's the first time
we ever hung out outside of work and it
just like made like a brotherly bond I
think a lot of that is I understand the
laws and I understand safety behind like
drugs and alcohol and weed and whatever
and I think it does it's very important
yeah I also think that a lot of us are a
little more self-reliant than the laws
make us seem like oh like whether
whether the laws are school or society
whatever wanted me to be completely
unaware of drugs until I'm 21
well I smoked weed when I was 15 yeah
so whether you want me to do that or not
like I'm around it like whether you want
me to pretend it's not there it's there
when I was 12 you know like yeah these
things we can't just pretend that
they're not around us yeah I don't cover
it up yeah I think we should learn about
it and I don't think that like a young
kid should be using drugs like I I kind
of wish that I had started like drinking
and stuff at a later age but and also I
but I think that talking about it and
and letting kids experience it and then
even as they're young instead of just
waiting till they're 26 or in whatever
like to talk about it later on yeah we
could talk about it right now
introspective from our age and they can
say like oh yeah like I'm only 19 and
I've been drinking for two years but
like yeah I don't know it's not I don't
want to do it this way or yes it's not
all this cracked up to be or whatever I
don't know it just explained it talking
about things that people actually go
through yeah oh yeah I mean I think that
people are starting to get it now in
this generation anyways by all those
freaking teen movies that are out you
know how it it's so weird because now
it's it's one of those things it's it's
normal now you know that kids are oh
this is what I see on TV it's always
been that way but it's I feel like it's
I don't know if it's because we're
getting older kind of thing it's like we
see it more often you know maybe it's
just because now we don't have those
blinders or whatever or you know no
one's telling us like what we can and
cannot do being this age now but for
kids it's it's out there I mean you got
your YouTube you got the movies that
like mm-hm
you can just stream off Netflix and
people kids are watching all this you
could notice a normals yeah it's like
you know like you know that the that
whatever drug whatever drug you can
think of that's in your brain when you
learned it when you were 17 yeah now
kids who are nine years old know about
it because YouTube they know about it
because social media they know about
like so this is the thing is kids know
about it we can pretend that they don't
yeah or we can talk about our
experiences with it yeah hey here's what
I because a lot of these like I hate
using the sentence but like a lot of
these drugs are helpful but a lot of
these drugs a lot of these
experiences like so that experience like
it's not like the the weed gave us that
experience our friendship our
camaraderie our the situation our our
laughter are you know like that those
things break down our ego and make us
think think dorky things sure but like
if drugs can give people those
situations like that's that's the
situation
I value with with my brothers like
that's that's a valuable situation that
I had in my life and at the time it was
something that was very found upon at
the time you know cuz we wasn't legal
back then yeah we were that old case
where that old but yeah we're gonna have
to start saying that we're gonna have to
start saying like oh yeah this is a
story what a weed was not legal yeah it
was illegal here my cool story man
that's super not interesting ya know
yeah this happened at a time when it was
frowned upon but we were sharing a bond
that like and so you're brave enough and
willing to take the risk of doing
something illegal with me mm-hmm
you know it's one of the how do you say
it's it's cool you have a friend if
you're billing your friend out right you
have a bro that's sitting next to you in
jail right it's almost like a that bond
but no people we don't like to be in
jail
none that I've been there don't want to
do it again yeah I've actually never
been to jail that's that's one thing
what situation
yeah not going what I've been there once
I'm very very level-headed I feel like
it's like police come around I'm just
like oh look I gotta talk to you I'm
gonna talk to them I'm gonna handle a
situation like I've always been that
[__] yeah like I've never been
like doing anything wrong but it's funny
you know you have these little dorky
situations like like so it's so that
actually that same graveyard
the mob breeding graveyard yeah when I
was in high school before this mm-hmm
before we had our venture where I
thought were 4x4 hanging over the graves
the grave the tombstones I we got caught
smoking like a potato and we were young
oh my god this is like in like I don't
remember exactly the details but I
remember what jurisdiction it was
anything but the police officers that
came up they came up and they were like
they were behind us and out of the cars
by the time we even knew they're behind
us like we're at the top ended up
they're like made us super scared they
like scared the [__] out of us like
I guess whatever and then they took the
pipe in the weed yeah it's like that
show when he's chucked at his heart rate
is that what it is maybe I don't know
that's what do into you know that that
is what they did yeah they're like like
so what should they like writing down
our names like we're gonna call your
parents and all this [__] like so all
the kids in the car just like please
don't whatever and then at the end what
he did I don't remember exactly but he
literally I think he took like the weed
in the pipe in his hand and he just
cocked back and he chucked as hard as he
could into the woods what he'd the
littered okay but I'm saying like he or
did he not throw the paraphernalia into
the shrubbery oh my gosh yeah it's weird
though I it's funny like I don't condone
that now like that's you know but these
are the sort of things like this is like
that that's like what your uncle would
do like if your uncle came in and he's
like seize all of you think the kids
smoking weed he'd be like hey I'm not
gonna tell your parents I'm throwing
this [__] in the woods get your [__]
together don't do this you know whatever
like yeah I like the cop can do that I
just remember that like it was a very
like cool moment and I'm sure that like
now I mean he was literally if like I
don't know who it was I remember George
is nothing but like he probably lose his
job over that [__] nowadays oh yeah you
definitely can't do that now because now
everyone has phones recording yeah the
whole situation yeah they're like I can
get Twitter famous and I record this cop
yeah I'm not getting me in trouble it's
like okay well how about he just like he
doesn't want to get you in trouble god
damn it he just wants it a better life
for you say hey I'm gonna set you on the
path of righteousness his path of
righteousness or whatever hey kid I
already know where this leads down to
he's seen that many times obviously if I
can get some young maybe I have made a
difference in this kid's life really
exactly I mean I yeah I obviously don't
remember his name you know I was a
younger punk kid but like dude that at
that moment was crazy especially like me
not having I didn't have at that age I
had zero adults in my life that I
trusted zero and so like cop whoever it
is whoever they're coming up I'm just
like how do i how do I just wonder my
ass out of this like that's learning my
situation like with any
interaction it was like how do I get out
of this or how do I do what I need to do
to control this situation like that was
like my little [__] that's what I would
do as a little [__] yeah but I didn't
have trust in adults and so little stuff
like that I'm gonna cop through the
through the weed into the into the
bushes and like said like get the hell
outta here you know like that stuff
that's so frowned upon I guess generally
now probably but yeah that's definitely
something gave me trust as a kid you
know yeah what which he did but what you
don't know is you were so high that he
switched the bag and here's something
else they took the freaking pipe and
they're like hey hazel yeah yeah he took
that weed he smoked it that night and by
the way officer if you're listening to
this and you remember this story he
still smokes weed yeah you didn't see me
you didn't say sorry but yes melted
joint before Ryan came over yeah
hey I'm also Ryan so I I do want to I
don't want to I'm just like talk about
drugs and I own this podcast because you
know a lot more than that I invited you
on here because your personality but I
do want to you I mentioned earlier and
I've been studying a lot about like the
like PTSD depression like with like
psychedelics and DMA Mali ecstasy MDMA
Mali next see those are all when I say
those three things let's say they're
interchangeable they're the same thing
so a lot of people are using a lot of
MDMA and psilocybin whatever like just
drugs - we're changing the way we think
of a lot of our drugs and we're out PTSD
and so I would like to talk about we've
mentioned briefly earlier so back in the
day on the same subject of drugs we
would have what we would call Mali
parties yes so this is something that
this is going to be if you've never
heard of this is it's a bit silly but
bear with us I think that if we describe
these I know it sounds dork and I know
it sounds very hippie but thinking of
the amazing crazy insane feelings that I
felt at these like at your home when we
were growing up this is years and years
ago way long joke oh yeah
they get all eight five nine eight five
nine yeah like you just like if if
people with PTSD people with depression
people who are lonely if you're
listening to this and you've never tried
any sort of like we're not gonna talk
about psychedelic said we're just
talking about MDMA for this one they're
doing a lot of research to hunt of
research on PTSD like people are I think
the statistic that I read was sixty
percent of the people who tried MDMA who
had PTSD had positive results on there
with one like sitting so sixty percent
it's like hey yeah PTSD it's not high
rating yeah so yeah anyway so I want to
talk about we would have Molly parties
and like I think you should have been
certain that house should have been
certified if like for PTSD people is my
dad and then he should have been a
counselors office oh it's you would
you'd become a different person the okay
so so let's let's go ahead and set the
stage so on the surface level Molly is a
drug just like ecstasy yeah so it makes
you feel nice a lot of people nowadays
if you're familiar with it and like
party songs or whatever it's something
that people take along with cocaine
whatever like it's it's just a party
like you're drinking you take some Molly
it makes you feel good it's a sex thing
whatever yeah but so when we had first I
just kind of dabbled isn't yeah cuz
Molly was just coming out or like it
came out like maybe a year before or
something yeah so my understanding of
Molly was that it was it's it's supposed
to be pure MDMA
yes so ecstasy is MDMA based but it also
has some ketamine some whatever the [__]
you want but you don't even see is a
press tab MDMA base to Molly based yeah
but it also has some other [__] that's
the reason yes that's the thing that you
don't know like that that's why they
what they call MD and taken Molly is
rolling you don't get that with ecstasy
cuz you're just hot I mean I guess you
can roll whatever you feel really but
you're just always [__] high it's
like you never come down and so the the
sling on rolling is that is that because
it's up and down like you like feel like
oh yeah well it all depends on how you
you know you take it but yeah usually
it's when you take
MDMA or Molly you just have this feeling
in your stomach and it starts and then
you get really lightheaded mm-hmm and
I'm not gonna get into like the
scientific terms you just feel [__]
good you feel [__] yeah and then you
come down in the middle of your roll and
you're like what the heck and you feel
kinda normal still kind of high
you know eyes buggin looks like you're
feeling a water bottle at Lightspeed
yeah and you're you're talking about
starting a podcast you're pressing all
of your ideas that you'll never complete
it's like cocaine but ten times better
yeah people probably haven't done
cocaine yeah all right trying to get
this okay you're wearing yeah so
basically it's that so and then also
when you when you hit your low you you
come right back up and then you're high
again and you start feeling good it's
like a feeling that I tried to explain
because how I feel is you know but at
the time I was listening to a lot of
music every type of music kind of thing
but I told people it feels like
listening to every single song your
favorite song that has made you like you
know your hair stand you know those
goosebumps when you listen to music you
know there's it's like every single song
that you ever heard your life played all
at once at the same time and you it's
like a culmination of those songs yeah
it's it's the it's the feeling of those
songs as oh yeah all in one like yeah I
think if you if you could I mean you
can't even imagine what that feels like
because you're just like oh that would
sound terrible all those all my favorite
song is it what's this house terrible
but like think about that feeling yeah
feeling of all those yeah and actually
the probably the best description that I
ever heard in my life of the that
feeling it was from Cody mm-hmm you can
bleep that out if you want to but he's
like say first names okay so Cody he's I
hit one time we're just you know we're
just smoking really high and he's like
you know what it feels like I'm like
what what feels like you can't just like
hear Butler that on the conversation
like he's like no taking Molly it's like
okay he's like it feels like we're
Adam and Eve like wait what are you
talking about he's like it's that
feeling of them discovering things for
the first time because they were the
first humans right supposedly the first
humans on earth so it's like almost like
a discovery like oh this is what grass
feels like order
wow man yeah like you know what I mean
like oh like eating an apple for the
first time it's like your first times of
everything you do you think it's you
know because I've been I've been super
into a lot of meditation yoga lately so
obviously like the present moment like
presents like yeah here now it's very
like it's something that's been a
revelatory experience for me as it turns
out do you think Molly almost emphasizes
your senses so well you can smell more
you can see more intently you can taste
of some sorts you can kind of taste
whatever you could hear more and usually
like it emphasizes all of your senses so
much to where it's almost an ultra
present moment oh yeah that's it yeah
that's it you know that's actually yeah
exactly how I don't think about any of
your [__] you don't think in forward
in the future you don't care what's
going on you care about living in right
moment Yeah right dude if you put you
put a [__] on Molly ins from
nice green grass grass you wouldn't care
if he was allergic to grass and he's
like frickin warhead and so swollen he's
like dude I don't know about you but
this [__] grass man well so you know
it's funny like okay so the the jokes up
on Molly like everybody like hears about
like oh actually like everything feels
good you know we've seen get him to the
Greek where you stroke in the wall with
Jeffrey like all this stuff but so yeah
thing about MDMA because I think I want
these conversations to be somewhat kind
of at least a little bit valuable like I
understand that we had a different the
world was different when we took it we
were doing it for party reasons but like
looking back it was very yeah we our
lives but now like people are gonna be
taking these like literally in a
counseling setting like people are going
to be pets and in some smart yeah like
that they're going to be in Averett like
it's gonna be more casual it's
psychedelic research I'm sure probably
places like this honestly you come here
and you got a dude like me who has
tattoos okay like this you got
remember it's like if they do they're
doing this on a scientific level like
sometimes it's like you're you know you
well in my head I always go way to movie
as kind of thing we're like they're in a
white room hey you're gonna be the next
I know two hours taking this Molly in a
lab coat that's like that's pretty
uncomfortable yeah do it like what
you're about to describe you know and
yeah you know in a comfortable setting
yeah I think that's I think it's super
important like because we're going over
the next 10 years a lot of the research
I've been doing this is showing that
over the next 10 years as a random
estimate the in the the changes with
like the research the we're doing a lot
of the research but it's going to be to
the point where like I said outside
earlier fifty-three old ladies who have
never touched drug in their life have a
drink out called a drink violence wanna
yeah they're going to be like okay I
just went through a divorce I'm like I
don't know what to do with my life and a
doctor is going to be to the point or at
some point whatever this is gonna look
like someone they're gonna have a
prescription or something for MDMA or so
siren or whatever it is like the people
are gonna need to know like what am I
getting into because this is so
different like like we casually use like
fun drugs recreationally yeah Marty when
you throw that all that stuff in there
and that just gets be turned off yeah so
like how do we how do we talk about like
so how do we correlate our experience
because so when we talk about these fun
experiences it's impossible for us to
not it's like oh yeah that's not funny
like you know like we're laughing it off
but how do we make how do we talk about
these experiences and make them not like
still scary and off-putting to people
who could really benefit because
thinking about now like we didn't think
about it back then but think about now
like like if you were they give you know
people with depression yeah like now
that we have these clinical like ideas
and like different dosages and what like
settings that was gonna be eventually
something like you would be like yeah
like you should totally try MDMA right
yeah you would could you would like if
your sister was depressed you'd be like
hey like you try it so how do we
correlate Ryan I guess I'm asking you
like how do we correlate the
conversation we're having from like the
fun party here's the experiences we had
how do we make that
sound comfortable for 53 year old ladies
who just got a divorce are like trying
to convince themselves to try this to
help themselves deal with the morning of
their divorce or the I mean like like
how do we take like how do they find
value from these conversations of us Oh
about taking like the Molly like as a
prescription drug I will because they do
to the next 10 years it's going to be a
normal thing yeah might be some sort so
hopefully like they have it down to our
like you know like the people that are
actually administering you know Molly
itself you know like obviously when we
talk about like you said we were talking
about partying so yeah we were taking
like a lot you know you're just like
whatever when that's the quitting is now
live hit yeah we worry I'm happy that we
were the guinea pigs like not that we
are like riding that [__] down but
there's plenty of [__] like us
yeah we're just taking whatever and we
know what's good what what bad amounts
are so like that probably helped I hope
so if they get it downs like if doctors
can get it down to where like you if you
can just take like a little bit amount
just enough to like feel something in
like you know it's like I don't know I
guess it would be like taking like a
depression pool but I don't know what
it's like to take a pill like that I do
what is it like I know okay so it's I'm
super happy to describe it sexually so
so like I so the first time I had taken
it so I had taken I had smoked weed I
had drank I had done ecstasy like I was
a but let's say casual punk kid at like
a good kid I guess but like I've done
recreational drugs I've done alcohol
whatever when I took so I got prescribed
I went into the doctor's office and I
literally you go in in within five
minutes you're you have a prescription
here and like you just tell them that
I'm sad and they gave me whatever so I
had SS are SSRI inhibitors mm-hmm
which what I mean you could look it up
but it's it it's depression medication
essentially it's so hard to describe how
it makes you feel because it's not like
the drugs that we've ever taken
it's not it makes you feel closest to
nothing that you can think of so
basically it turns off like your emotion
inhibitors or something or kind of is
well so and i don't want i'm afraid that
any listener this might scare the way
for it and I think that there's tons of
people and I know a lot I know more
people than not people I know probably
ninety percent of people that I know
that I've tried depression medication
have had good success with it so if
you're listening and you think maybe you
should try it
give it a goddamn try don't listen to me
but for me it was terrible I had a
terrible time to pressure medication
it was the most disconnected feeling I
felt I had this weird the way that I can
describe it I couldn't feel sad I
couldn't feel empty but I knew that I
should I knew that I should I'm like oh
this is where emptiness would go and it
felt as if that was taken from me and
and that's how I felt like I was like
that's how like my mental state was on
this medication and so that that's where
like so they say like suicidal thoughts
get very prevalent like that's how I was
like okay this is this is where that
sparks want it's like not even helping
yeah
this may take away all your feelings so
hope you can deal with it so it's not
that intense though because when I first
I mean there was times where I really
did feel good like you feel like it
makes it to where your highs aren't so
high and your lows aren't so low which
for a while that is nice because
sometimes you get to a point where
you're like dude I've been either
incredibly happy or incredibly depressed
for the last like these two feelings
like where can I find a happy medium
you're [__] hardcore on the gas
hardcore it breaks yeah exactly it's
like you can't live life like that
that's like to me right now you just
described it like I don't like that I
wouldn't I would hate that cuz no like
you know me it's like you know I've I've
never been on any medication or whatever
but I've been through depression and you
know had those crazy weird suicidal
thoughts I don't want to call it weird
I'm sorry but you know because a lot of
people feel these feelings but no
they're weirdest [__] it's super weird
it's the second yeah I hate getting to
that point so I like I said I don't know
I never went to a doctor or whatever but
I knew that I wasn't feeling any plate I
don't take the same way
my solo right now like yeah you know cuz
I felt really how do you know who you
know we have a sense of who we are like
you're like wait like I appreciate I'm a
happy ass dude like I'm not these aren't
my feelings like what's that you know
yeah exactly so it's like me like I hate
what hate to say this way but it's like
man I can't believe I made it this far
in life for like feeling the things I
felt and like and the thoughts that
would just go through my him I do that's
not even worth it anymore so like for me
to hear that feeling of like you know
like you said like some people you know
taking these depression pills yeah it
has worked but what what happens to the
people that doesn't work you know or
they just on another pill that makes
them even worse and I sound like you're
just like your body's not even normal
anymore you know it's full you're just
pumped full of drugs and trying to make
you feel a feeling and well in its right
ones suit it's so scary because you get
to the like so like I had I had this
moment I think I'm actually meant to
this one here before but I had this
moment where I had a reddit comment
actually like pull me out of this like
so I was feeling kind of good like so I
had up my dose I had tried a couple
different essays I think they were all
everything that I tried or the doctor
gave me and they're all SSRI inhibitors
if that changes I'll come back to the
podcast and chocolate I think they're
all it is alright knitters so I got like
a higher dose cuz he said he kept saying
like no I think this is the one just
keep like it would be like go to him a
couple weeks later because what they do
is they give you here's this dose coming
back to me in three weeks what a week or
two happen whatever it was and I'm like
I don't feel good this not good I feel
crazy like please know in like he
doesn't really like what does he can do
what can he possibly do like he's not
therapist he's living my old family
doctor from when I was a kid like I
really I feel bad for the guy like hid
the positions that doctors are put in
now for this stuff ik he's no
psychiatrist he doesn't know what I
really need yeah it doesn't have enough
time to talk to me like he's yeah he's a
guy to remedy whatever's going on as of
right now yeah what are you feeling
oh well head stuff that's not my I know
I mean in email very comfortable but he
only has five minutes yeah you know but
anyway so anyway so I read this comment
on reddit I was feeling good my doses
were kind of like I was it had been
probably only
weeks to where I was like I almost had
forgotten that I was taking the
medications outside of I had some some
gnarly side effects like sleep was an
issue and then I had I was constantly
sweating always sweating like my legs
were just constantly sweating which is
crazy that terrible [__] thing yeah but
uh I read this comment on reddit that
said I was on depression medication
something about it would have been nice
but then I realized that none of it was
real and it wasn't actually me feeling
good it was the drugs that were making
me feel normal
it was something like that like some
sense that was very blunt like yeah it's
not me doing it the the drugs that are
making and it clicked something in me
and it was like my depression was like I
control your life now like it was like
this terrible clicking thing yeah so so
for me like in that so those are moments
where I think that like the suicidal
thoughts that they like warned you about
on on TV and stuff I think those are the
moments where it's like you should kill
yourself for now yeah like it like it's
so I felt that I grasped that and I was
like oh no and then this is stupid and
any listeners don't do this do not do
this but I cold turkey it's like oh like
I just stopped yeah I heard you're not
supposed to do that yeah it wasn't even
I was I honestly I don't remember
honestly I don't remember like laying on
the ground like having withdrawal Senate
on mine people are like oh it's horse
hair withdrawals it's worse than like
blah blah like I I know that I kept
casually I kept drinking I had probably
done cocaine within the last couple
weeks after like quitting it like at
least once but like not that I like did
cocaine every day or something yeah like
just casually I kept partying and I
think that I was just in such a state of
self hate and oppression that like it
just was adding on like my withdrawals
or whatever you would call it yeah
you're just like rolling up your head
with it everything should I was it was
it was just more like yeah but things
suck right now that's cool yeah I feel
shitty I always feel shitty cool yeah so
that's that was this beer like you know
hang out with a bunch of people make me
feel a lot better like replacing maybe
avoid the crowd to have maybe if I can
just avoid if I lay down too long I sore
thing about so let's not sleep as much
as I can all these things I did distract
myself but yeah so so that's the the way
that it feels to pressure medication for
me anyway and everybody feels different
so you got to take it slow
if you need to try it if your doctor
thinks you to try it somebody a family
thinks you can try it try it but yeah
for me it made me very honestly a little
bit comparable to do a weed high okay a
you're not fully you're kind of just a
little bit of a numb like you kind of
just a little bit of stagg like you're
just a little bit mmm okay it's like
it's um like more like some noise that
you can't even like pitch to this like
you know once I hear this noise you're
like it's not miserable it's not happy
yeah
it's not because when you think of our
brains when we think of like oh you
didn't feel anything or no it's not
super-happy we think of that sounds
scary that feels comfortable it's not
that it's like you feel miserable all
the time but it's this this weird
in-between feeling and some people just
it just doesn't right it didn't work for
me I remember I had a I was at the first
week and I had a hair appointment and
I'm friends with my that lady who cuts
my hair she's awesome yeah and she was
talking to me and then at some point I
kept up with the after a while but then
like the medications really started to
kick in I started getting like I didn't
really want to talk and she's like
pointed it out I mean she like said
something she's like what's wrong like
you're acting weird and like I obviously
don't want talking like whoa I wanted a
really high dose of freshmen occasion
cuz I'm trying not to blow my [__]
brains out when I go home yeah like
obviously if I tell you and I remember
like like realizing that I had to
explain it to other people like why I
was acting weird I like maybe like why I
kind of look like I was on drugs or
whatever it was I goes on a high dose of
whatever but like that moment realizing
that I had to explain it was like oh
yeah like how do you talk to it like
someone like you barely know and say
yeah oh by the way I'm acting like this
because of well why would she probably
been super cool
she really would anybody a lot of people
would be like maybe a little caught off
guard at first but give them a few
seconds to get some bearings and
honestly I've noticed that people are
like yeah okay oh yeah so my uncle took
two freshman you know you type two types
of people or three types one more like
oh I feel the same way one is they had
they know someone of it the third one is
let me tell you of how you should feel
and like oh that's just a feeling that
you just got
tell yourself in the morning every like
I'm happy right now it's like something
about like my dad used to tell me it's
like I don't get why people would kill
themselves or whatever all this [__]
and he's like you know you just wake up
you look in the mirror until your self
you're happy I'm like I don't think it
works like that well that's one of the
answers I hated the most
you know and it's something I never
wanted to talk to my dad about like
still to this day I haven't really told
him but like he knows that like I am
very an emotional man
mm-hmm he knows that I can be like
pretty like suit like you know super
happy or I could be just like I wouldn't
say a word he's like do it was wrong
like I don't lo-lo's her like yeah you
know I never had like a that happy
medium you know not until now you know
it's one of those things you just got a
were like what sucks is like I I never
have taken any pills I never went to a
doctor about it you know or talked it's
like I'm just happy I'm one of those
people I had my I had my friends you
know I had really good friends like you
you know and you know now I have my wife
and like people who cared about me
enough to say that like holy [__] like
you know what I need to get myself out
because if I don't either I'm gonna be
left behind and gone you know or I can't
be with the people I love the most right
you know and that like hurt me so much
I'm like dude I you know what I almost
gave in to like what my dad's like I
just got look in the mirror and to say
hey I'm happy blah blah blah you know
just like you know it's a I took in a
little bit of every what everyone said
you know like those three people that I
hated the most like like maybe maybe if
I take that all in at the same time
maybe I can figure this out you know
which I still till this day I a field of
like the low lows I still feel the high
highs you know but at the same time it's
like now I I got people that care about
me right what like I there's no way I
like now have my wife and a kid on the
way you know it's like holy [__] I don't
want to be that guy yeah I want to stick
around for the oh man I can't wait to
see like my future kid you know and
and be with my wife for the rest of my
life in you know even with my friends
and family like what was holy crabs like
if I do this right now it's like because
I see my friend and like kill himself
but you know but he he passed away at
such a young age and I saw the impact he
had I'm like you know I'm not saying
like I'm like him because I guy was
incredible but you know it's like what
what are the repercussions of me doing
that so you know letting the depression
win and the effects that it has on
people yeah got it you got a you know
it's funny like I realized that just by
standing up and fighting and just by the
living your life like you just by
getting married in in love and Katie in
and loving your life and taking what
your dad told you when you were younger
and thinking about it now like just by
living your life you are encouraging
others to do the same okay
I've ever thought of that new aren't you
yeah you get you give people permission
to fight by fighting you know like like
I guess that's another thing that I want
to have with this podcast is just be
like hey like you know [__] we're all
going through some [__] but like we're
pushing through and if you need to take
some energy if you need to take some
power from us pushing through like here
take it yeah take it you know yeah so
yeah that's come in yeah we got it we
got to keep pushing we got to keep like
no we don't [__] always know the
answers but they seem like they kind of
lay themselves out later in life if you
just keep like yeah just go in yeah
definitely like for the kids you know
like because we were so young going
through this crap you know it's like now
everyone's going through like anxiety
and stuff like that but they're going at
it in the wrong way like you know what
we kind of did we filled those voids or
whatever with something wrong like I
know that like you know some drugs not
saying that like you know later on maybe
like you said we were talked about
earlier like MBA could help you know you
know like it service those it's it's
rounded to go like right I would say in
ten years it's going to be literally
like a pharmacy thing oh I would hope so
I mean it's it's the most amazing
feeling that you ever feel you know like
but like we were saying earlier they
don't hopefully you know it's like
here's three hits you might feel a
little down in the morning but those
memories that you have to yeah as long
as you just remember the memories you'll
be good yeah just hold onto those
memories like so they just give you a
Rumspringa situation they're like you're
gonna go to a rave here's a couple of
festival tickets you're gonna you're
gonna cleanse your ego yeah stop being
[__] sad take this [__] and you may
go to have a good night bro yeah just
and then after that just hold on to
those memories and it'll make you happy
for the rest of your life okay so what
is it okay wait let's get let's get more
detailed with MDMA okay what's what is
it about MDMA so so my one of my very
like so I had an experience on MDMA and
that literally changed me as a person in
that sounds scary to any listeners if
you've never taken any sort of drugs I
know that sounds so [__] weird and
scary and uncomfortable and you don't
want that at all but this is a very good
thing I actually had a moment the sounds
hippie but it had good benefits in my
life I had my best friend at the time
Ian Fulton's it just could gotta be
around and then I was dating meditating
girl back in high school
mm-hmm all right I love you should
probably what that anyway so anyway
okay so so back in the day I was with
one of my good friends in a girl that I
was dating back in high school we had
taken MDMA we were literally outside on
the grass I'm not kidding this is
something we didn't know much about and
he I don't even know how much we took I
don't even know what it was something we
knew nothing about but we were on the
grass and I literally had moments where
we were all sitting there we weren't
talking where I was kind of looking
around joining another company
yeah I was in the grass and I had this
thought to myself not even like a high
like she do you dare to do it yeah it
was a I enjoy this grass right now like
this grass laying here with my elbow on
the grass with my two very close friends
this is a wonderful beautiful this is
what life is about this is great I have
this time when I was like I should
generally appreciate grass more and I
remember I had this time where even at
that moment I'm new
it was laughable like dorky thing but I
was like this is like actually a real
this is something I can take with me to
sober life to regular the we're at rest
my world is I should appreciate these
two people I should appreciate my
friends more I should appreciate things
like grass more and honestly I think you
know is ever lasting effects but for
like the the months afterwards I was on
like a euphoric like I'm appreciating
things more because Molly
because MDMA kind of shuts down here
like default mode Network it shuts down
your your your ego like moves around in
your brain it's done it's you're good to
just see what's in front of you so for
me around somebody first times it really
helped me in the moment realized that
what I have in front of me is great the
grass my friends whatever that sounds
dorky but yeah everlasting effects of
being able to be present and being able
to look at the things around me and be
like you know I am grateful that I have
a garage like you don't think goodness
I'm in collage that's nice yeah I'm a
basketball hoop thing like I didn't have
a basketball hoop my whole life growing
up like I have a basket that's so cool
the it helps you appreciate a little
like the tiniest things yeah do you have
any experience I would have to say
probably the best experience that I knew
that I realized in like holy crap this
this drug this Molly was awesome was
when we were all up there I wish you
were there to actually for this one
where when we're actually doing this but
we were sitting in a circle up in
remember but we called thugz mansion up
there in the freaking attic well yeah
it's supposed to be an attic but we
totally cool dude it was like bleh it
was like blankets and stuff yeah
blankets and my and you worked in the
movie theater and so there was cool ass
movie all we had I had every movie
poster you can think about they were
this sick and they were the ones that
like everybody wants right like they're
like you go to movie theaters you're
like oh do that say oh I had sick of
sick what was awesome like when you got
in that room you would have to like even
for me people I am only five five and a
half and yes I will always cherish that
half but anyways I would like I would
have to be ducking a little bit just a
little bit just to get in this room and
you know everyone else was like bent
over to try to get but as soon as you
laid down
like we had like all those pillows and
blankets gonna wash all the time because
we had people over like we were worried
sick hippy so like yeah no gross you
know it was clean oh we clean that nice
clean environment oh it was it was a
bunch of bros but like every take care
of it dude okay take two take the care
to read instead of it no but essentially
this was like a crawl at an attic that
you can duck in but almost walk in yeah
but it was covered in blankets the stuff
but not like dirty like it was like I
can't have you walk around the corner
and you just like oh my god this is so
yeah it was rad and they had the door to
open and look like a freakin old western
door that you like Paulo what the bar
remember that it had like a little hook
but it looked like a freakin yeah like a
door from like the from the West or
something like a western movie you're
like just kick it open you're like I'm
here I'm here but anyways so we were
going we were laying in a circle kind of
everyone's just sitting up there just
you know for summer we just hit like we
weren't like our high high we like you
know we're like where he goes yeah we
were past the peak and then for some
reason I just yelled like not yelled but
I was like hey guys we should all say
something nice to each other and so that
we like we took turns and I'm like hey
you know let's say you know when crystal
was a little boy doesn't like hey
everyone we're gonna take turns and
we're gonna say something really nice to
crystal like how she affected your life
or why she's so important to you and we
did that with everybody and I swear when
we came out of that room break something
that oh it turned like everyone's mood
like we went from like you know just
kind of like hanging out partying on a
thing to like we went downstairs and you
know like how when you're on it you know
you're always like oh so hives and stuff
but we're at a when we start rolling
again we weren't like crazy anymore you
know we were just sitting there like so
just chill like you know and then we
just kept talking like like me you are
right now but we were just feeling good
it's there
there's no negative response everything
you know smartass remarks it was just
people hanging out and loving each other
yeah so so what is the I think the
negative annotations with with MDMA with
ecstasy like with the media is always
like it's very like sexual it's always
so well used like I don't even know if
I've ever had sex on a man yeah actually
I really don't think I have but it's
honestly I'm sure it makes whatever
you're doing better like I'm sure sex on
him he means walking oh I never have
either yeah but I don't want to ruin it
so all right I'm sorry I have no no
that's why I've heard a ton of people
say that it's like hey don't do it on
him do you make you do it off it's it's
not but I I mean I don't know we got sex
is like pizza I like sex it's just cool
yeah sex is great it's like I I think
that the the sexual like it's not like
you take xsa you take an MDMA take Molly
you just start like rubbing the dude
next to you you rub like the girl that's
really yeah it's not really like that I
mean it's it's it's an amplification of
your environment and it also shuts off
your I think it shuts off your default
mode Network so your ego is out of the
way so think of in that situation to
where like imagine you're at like
whoever you are listening to this year
with you're with Ryan Santos in a room
you feel kind of good you fill this new
drug like I like I'm happy and he says
hey we should look around we should you
know say something we like about each
other we should look chill in the eyes
right in the face and say you know what
do you like about me like like what
something awesome about me like that you
and your friend groups you would not say
you wouldn't just be having some blood
lights with your boys and say like hey
yeah hey Stevie yeah you got beautiful
eyes and honestly the way you treat your
sister is very respectable thank you
yeah i you know that doesn't happen all
it is is like you talk [__] about each
other I'm talking about okay in you I
know you mean well you know you mean
well but so the thing about the mmm it's
oh so these moments if you're listening
in it you know [__] if for whatever
reason if this is later in life or
whatever if somehow somehow MDMA is
legal or you have a way of safely
getting it like I don't condone illegal
use of anything of course but a like
create the environment with you and your
friends like honestly like try not do to
its some rave and like people they talk
to you but you know you explained it
earlier
about like oh you takin like ghosts and
you're filling up on somebody it's like
no because you're you're in that
environment like one leg we never I
guess we had those shows just starting
to like be more popular like the EDM
what was there but it wasn't there yet
and so it's not like we went out to like
all these shows and like oh whatever we
threw these parties just with their
really good friends and if you wanted to
come join an experiment with Molly
itself like hey come on over we'll show
you the time yes so what is so what is
is there a world where you know again
assuming these things will be legal in
the next few years whatever where you
can get your friends together regardless
of who you are as a person regardless of
what you're trying to experience get
together with a bunch of friends and
take MDMA like so we would literally
have back in the day into your house
we'd have Molly parties yeah I think we
did that calmly party oh yeah that's all
[__] the name we're just Molly party
yeah Molly parties man it's so dude I
mean so what we would do honestly again
these are cool stories and I certainly
want to share them because they're cool
but I really am emphasizing like you
know coins it seems to any listener and
I am emphasizing because I think that
these things like I had a traumatic
childhood experience like I had I had I
had rough times to childhood and these
are things that I think saved me and
like helped me mm-hmm
loved my life more than I could have
ever even thought up you know like it
like we had such good times but so
anybody who's able to like him in the
future imagine like if people are you
know people have wine parties now
50-year old ladies like oh come on over
well we'll have some appetizers and
we'll watch if I can I don't know Golden
Girls yeah whatever like but do you like
you can have a thing like hang out with
your friends and you can take MDMA yeah
I do it safely and you could all like
you know or even just with you and your
husband or you and what are the prisoner
you and a counselor if this is the way
that things are going like I don't know
these Molly party's men we would get
everybody together and just have the
funnest not only a funnest time but like
the most loving time like yeah if you
walked into if we were having a moment
party imagine 10 people on MDMA and
we're just having great conversation
honestly that's probably the base of it
if you walked in you would just see five
different very intricate
wonderful conversations oh but you feel
that love when you are through the door
like exactly people open up man it's
like that door of being shy or you know
like something that you've lived for
your whole life of like not being able
to talk you know and I really like
that's like totally not me I've always
been like you know two feet in the mouth
man you can still to this day you can't
shut me up but there's like people I've
known that actually lived with us that
you've never really talked and they get
down to like the down-and-dirty of what
they've been through and you know it's
not like we sat there and cried to each
other or something all right we were
just like you know if you did honestly
it would be like a Coulomb that would
just hit that like let's do something
cool like it would be that cool oh yeah
oh yeah fantastic you know it's like hey
you know what you got it out you talked
about like something you never wanted to
talk about but like that person would
like even new people that would come
over then didn't live with us you know
when we had these Mali parties would the
next day like either you knew or like
other people were just like that was the
best night of my life I never knew you
could do this kind of stuff without
having like the whole sexual innuendos
of like you know or just like oh yeah
like a rager kind of thing we were just
like relax I just I never understood the
whole hey like I you know I've done it
you know good like this was afterwards
but like go to a rave or something at my
party man I don't know yeah that's
missing out something so yeah well so
that we were talking about that before
here too
I've been a DJ for a long time and so
like I see being a DJ for a long time
when I say that a lot of times it's kind
of like remember where I'm at I'm the
sober person behind the decks yeah on
the Saturday nights on the Friday nights
when I still feel that he's done play
this no I mean no but like so I see the
last 10 years of my life has been I'm in
the corner as a surveillance camera I'm
my job is to look around like I'm
playing the song and playing this five
do people like it so my job every three
minutes is to look around and inspect
the room so for the last Friday and
Saturday of the last ten years
I've been every 3 minutes inspecting
every room that I've been in yeah you
know as a DJ like so crazy so it's it's
hard for people to think about like that
way you know and I'm in that makes
people uncomfortable actually like if
you really can't put it that way I guess
but this guy has evidence he's recorded
a ha ha ha yeah [__] that we did
taking photos if you're listening to
this I have a photo of you probably
maked no I mean I I just Christie we
have fun - yeah photo of you Christie I
actually have your phone so if you can
have had it for six months
who's Christie your boyfriend cheating
on you yeah yeah Steve yeah I saw him at
the club I always do know that bastard
that cheating bastard
no but but but I see so so I have seen
the before I started DJing before I ever
even touched the [__] before I ever
started eating before anything I had
taken MDMA had taken money had gone to
festivals yeah but I had also before
that I had gone to your house and
experienced the love on another level
that I had never felt before
yeah especially I was like a kid can we
talk about when you were there and
you're pulling people into my room oh my
god we need to talk about that let me
tell you how much love he was feeling
that night guys
you'll tell you in a second this is
great all right you only tell it tell it
ok so so listen listeners if you have
heard the song affect most people
probably heard home by Edward Sharpe and
the Magnetic Zeros
home let me go this is great thank you
one song right so the album of that song
is on he's the [__] best out like
it's so good oh so it was amazing so
this song came out and I was at this
time my life this was I had gone from
and probably honestly listening to a lot
of like Linkin Park and like like more
hip-hop kind of like angry of Lestat
Killswitch Engage was very into like
Metal Mulisha and this was kind of my
first I've liked everything the whole
life all this music was the first time I
disappeared it's like this like super
hippie stuff for me like this is a chill
folk music like very nice yeah so at
Ryan's
party that day I went to the store I
bought the album like I bought this
physical CD like it came with a poster I
think hell yeah I think he had it
pre-planned or something like I already
know it's gonna happen this is probably
like a very plan thinking to me honestly
III feel like dingy wait did you buy it
that day or did you buy it like a couple
days before and then you listened to it
I don't know I can't remember but I just
Tobi did it honestly yeah I know it felt
like it was that day I don't know either
way I had recently bought this bought
this album Edward Chapman next zeros I
forget the name of the the but at home
now remember I don't know the name but I
would say the album so what I would do
how many people you think read that
party like 20 max no actually you know
what maybe new 30 no we never had that
many people over with yeah wasn't yeah
it was only like usually comes in the
teens but that night we did actually a
lot of people I don't know so it's so
either way we were so what we do we're
all rolling we're all having a good time
every is in their own world and I went
in Ryan's room and I locked myself in
there and I put on his TV I put on the
album and I would play the album and
what I would do is I would go into the
party and I would walk up to people and
I mean I was I would I thought it was
the best thing oh it was the best thing
ever that I whispered if you're gonna be
doing this you know whisper in someone's
ear whether you're on Molly or not and
then drag them into the room and it's
totally dark and they're like is that
the little 32 inch TV I had to do it was
a portal it was a portal you know it's
cool I've always created these portals
for people in my life that I've I'm glad
that I'd do it for a living now but I
this album was so it honestly it meant
so much to me like it was such a great
album at the time anyway but like
honestly on on Molly you feel like you
really understand on on when you take
these drugs when you really have well
your analytical brain shuts down take
the time to like yeah listen or - yeah
or like so think about songs that you
think is beautiful
think about why you think it is
beautiful you don't really know
but when you're on MDMA you have
assessed over your like I don't know why
it's beautiful but that is so okay and
I'm gonna let myself I'm not gonna let
myself say like I need to know why it's
beautiful before I feel any more
beautifulness you say I'm gonna feel
whatever I want to feel with for no
reason so it's like you've let yourself
feel it beautifulness I mean that's
weird but anyway so I would play through
this album I would show like a couple
specific songs and the person whoever
they were whatever state they were in in
the first place they would literally
just melt their face would melt in this
room oh it was a person I'd like I gotta
show you this yeah I well I was watching
people coming out of that room like what
are they doing I'm like like every 15
minutes thirty minutes my party here and
it's but by the way it's male and female
coming out of this room what is
happening and then all of a sudden you
finally asked me am i okay I got to find
out what the hell is happening in there
you take me in and I can't even remember
what song that you're showing me I'm
pretty sure home was one of them and
then you showed me a couple other songs
and I just remember just sitting sitting
back and then just closing my eyes and
just in like I can I can never listen to
any of those songs normally yeah kind of
like it was like that and then there's
another song when you weren't there when
someone blasted I think it was Darren
one night he's like do yellows in the
song I'm like okay and it was freaking
Michael Jackson man in the mirror and
all song is like you haven't heard this
way it's like we've all heard it dude
what the heck but when you're on Molly
it's like holy [__] it was different but
did that time when it was the way that
you just pulled everyone like you're
having like an individual like
connection with everyone at this party
and showing all these songs of that
album man I like I said I can't listen
to that album again ever itching it that
just the way the melody was and I you
know what I wouldn't have never listened
to them if it wasn't for that night
right and I do that's so cool to me that
makes me so excited like yeah like
because I just remember like I loved it
and you know you know what it was too is
I was at that age I was very
like I've always been a popular guy but
I was very low and honestly like I was
very like I've always been popular like
honestly like that's a weird thing to
say out loud that's a weird thing to
even like stay it's a as a matter of
fact it's like when you know you know I
yeah but I like there's also like even
my best [__] friends that have known
me forever they will agree with you I'm
not like them like a I'm just different
like so when I'm able to like say like
wow like there's something that like
like do other people feel this much
beauty when they listen to music because
I don't think I'm allowed to talk about
it because I can made fun of and so when
I'm able to like obviously the drugs
like of course like yeah like makes you
just [__] fill things another level
but like I love that album so much and
the fact that there was a first time in
my life at a young age I was priced 16
or so that I can bring people and be
like hey like this gives me like a fit
like is this okay to feel like do you
feel this and like you guys are like you
have that thank you for sharing that and
I'm like wow like you value my
friendship you know so it's something
that like you guys like you bringing me
into your guys's friendship group man
was just like yeah it's so great and
then able to be myself in moments like
that oh yeah exactly and that's what I
loved about it dude it's like we were it
it was the house and by the way this
house we almost had for like almost two
years I think her it's like a year and a
half but I don't think it was longer
than that I didn't it we did a lot of
stuff in the house haha it was like it
was every weekend it's not saying that
we have Molly parties every weekend
people but no but we had we had friends
there
yeah it was a drink and stuff like that
you know like weed smoke but it like
there was all it was kind of just like
this is where you went yeah it's like
I'm hung in the thing was a little fun
fact that there was never a fight there
really there was no fistfights there's
no arguments I could see that so plainly
to like yeah no way there'd be a fight
there yeah yeah I mean there's like
after I think we're when we're moving
out and stuff like that they're like a
couple like arguments about like random
stupid [__] you just you know it's water
in a bridge right yeah it's it's like
when you get too close to someone after
that you can like me to have that
feeling fo I can say this to you because
I'm comfortable enough but then Elite so
fight it's like being a relationship you
know but out of like I was surprised
like wow
usually when you have a house like this
is always a fight there's always some
[__] that was not invited
you know gets mad at somebody and you're
like dude why did you bring Jimmy
everyone knows Jimmy kiss a dick and so
ya don't that never happened and so cuz
we've each other yeah it was round cuz
we had like it doesn't matter who you
were we had Hicks over there we had like
people that just like you know everybody
yeah everybody was welcome there oh it
sorry that I said Hicks alright but we
live in a town oh yeah that's another
funny thing we got to explain so like
like Sarge our terminology talking to
because I actually had so Hicks I
actually have said the term redneck and
I had a lady on the plane last year at a
lady like give me this whole spiel about
it's very offensive to st. rednecks do
you know that how redness is like if I
say in Castle Rock there's rednecks
that's offensive
Oh someone be offensive is it that
because like they went down like what
that word actually meant I think yes
well it means a back well if I remember
right it's like back in the day it's the
rednecks were the people that actually
worked out in the fields outside they
were screwed over by the banks yeah the
lesser people they were considered like
hey I make more money or just be [__]
you just work out in the fields here's
ready if you have redneck from me Ephram
yeah from the Sun and everything so well
so it's funny I'm sure that is the
definition but I mean the way that we've
grown up Mike you crew up and toodle
like it like class of 50 buddy yeah I
had people at my senior year flying that
flag Confederate flag and those and
those guys had no idea what that flag
actually really meant and I hated them
for it I was like that's the thing the
idea about history it's actually painful
cuz it's like you kind of want to just
let them like okay will you just be an
idiot but also like you need to know
mm-hmm I don't know no yeah it's it's
it's stupid I mean definitely I kind of
got like growing up you know being
Filipino you know dark-skinned Filipino
and
you know growing up in total class of 50
out in the freaking sticks and you just
have these sorry to say Hicks but if
that's the case is a I hope not but
someone will find it offensive right if
you find it offensive please leave that
in the comment below and if I give
enough comments I started getting money
I think so comment yeah it's so funny
because someone actually told me about
being offended by things he's like you
know what how this how of usually if
you're not offended then I'm offended so
it's like if yeah like you're not you
yeah if you're not I'm offended if
you're offended then I'm not offended
it's like people are like I was telling
you earlier something like person told
me it was like hey can you not see Jesus
Christ in front of me right and I was
like wait what he's in you know I'm
known him for a while now and I was like
he's like yeah I don't like you saying
my Lord saviors name in vain and then I
you know I'm a super nice guy I was
gonna you know and I just said okay
whatever
you know I'll stop saying it but I
almost I almost had the thing to say
well you can't make any more Asian jokes
to be yeah exactly like Asian like you
say you get to choose what I say with my
language can offend your beliefs but but
supposed to be cool with ya I'm supposed
to be cool with you saying it's like I'm
not offended but like dude you know
i-i-i almost want to give him the exact
example you know it's like hey man the
thing is is like if I say that I'm
actually be offended because you are
saying something about Who I am right
and then I bet you mean further yeah and
then it's like you know Jesus Christ is
like well that's my believe I'm like oh
so you're throwing your religion at me
now he's and then in he I know he try to
explain he's like I'm not probably
religion and stuff like that I just like
it I like that the relationship that I
have with Jesus Christ God and stuff and
I said well can you look I wanted to say
can you look up religion for me because
I'm pretty sure it means believing in a
higher power well okay it's I mean I I
think oh now we're going to deep waters
now I mean that people are about to get
a super offended
here we go mother oh ho I mean because
I've become quite a spiritual man last
year yeah I wouldn't say I'm and I just
I mean I don't give a fine [__] about
Ray labels I'm definitely just but I
think choosing what someone else says
with their mouth is insane that's not
something you can ever choose so when
you said whatever the situation was you
probably just it was a casual I don't
Jesus Christ like oh you know someone
walks around the corner too fast a cat
jumps and they get all sketchy like cats
do yeah any coke Jesus [__] guys yeah
like you didn't mean to say like this
situation is unimportant in terrible to
me and I'm equated that to your belief
in Jesus Christ yeah you did not say
that you said here's a sound that's
coming out of my mouth because I was
just startled really quick or whatever
the situation was they don't get to say
like hey what you said actually means
this I understand that that same
situation would like to say like the N
word yeah like we can say that same
situation for the N word and it doesn't
make sense like yeah it just casually
say the N word because you were startled
by a cat come around the corner but like
there's got to be some sort of give this
guy that you're talking about that was
like can you please not say the Lord's
name in vain
he knows god damn well god damn well I
said that that you did not mean yeah hey
I'm trying to insult your religion if he
personally does not want to take the
Lord's name in vain that's his choice
other than that he can't control he do
what he can also do while he's standing
next to you while he's standing next to
you you can pick up a cat and you could
punch it right in the [__] face he
can't do it it's not his he's not
controlling what you're doing yeah
exactly you can do whatever you want and
I think that we do have this fine line
of like here's what I think you mean do
you mean this like like because we can't
just say like well I meant this and it
was fine but he knows I'm sure om well
it's yeah I mean something bad it's like
either I can get an argument with this
guy you know it's like how do I get an
argument about my you know with a friend
saying there's this [__] that it
even doesn't even freaking matter I'm
like dude why are you pushing this on
like he wasn't pushing it's just like
the fact that he just
like went out and said that like enough
to say I'm like holy [__] like you're
the one who always talks about how
people are always offended by so many
things and you go off to my face and say
you were offended by this I'm like holy
[__] people who put Jesus Christ
Jesus [__] is this [__] I was
like holy crap you know I was like it's
not even worth it because he's one of
those guys it's like you know when you
meet those people that you just know
that they have to be right kind of thing
they have to always be the like the
one-upper I like I'm he is he's not like
saying I'm better than you but he always
just like oh I know you like that
restaurant that's stupid like go to this
he's the one who knows everything yeah
he's that guy he's got some experience
yeah and I'm just like dude stop I'm not
looking for advice buddy like cool like
that's oh that's your opinion
I think people and don't understand that
their opinions are not right yeah like
like your opinion is that's what you
think is you just you yeah man and with
what the funny thing is actually about
that is like he hates when he's like oh
would you want this this or this I'm
like I don't care he's like what do you
mean you don't care and I'm sorry I'm
about to get now I'm gonna be sexist my
dude why yeah like why why he being a
girl right now way better girl like what
you you're acting worse than my
ex-girlfriend like why why you only care
so much about what's something that
doesn't even [__] matter and it's
it's thing it's so trivial
all right the things that he cares about
so much that everything he's everything
huh almost has to be perfect and I'm
like stop you want to know why you
haven't adjusted and really stressed out
and all this stuff you know what being
stressed and stuff and weird about
stupid stuff and that do that [__] with
your body I know it does it really you
sit here and you clench you you tighten
your stomach you type your muscles you
stress yourself out you do we hurt our
body when we try to just clench like
yeah it's like controlling affect like
that's the one emotion being stressed
out like I how I used to be I used to be
so stressed like like him like but I was
younger this guy
like freakin 47 or something like dude
if you don't calm down
really quick and light just let just
start living life and stop caring about
what other people do yeah it's like well
I think that you know it's funny I used
to like over think about like whatever
you can't control you know you can't
control the outcome of other people what
other people do like I can't no matter
how this conversation goes
I can't control what you say Ryan like I
can't control how the end of this goes
like I can't go and if you're a tennis
player you can go in and say either I'm
going to win this match or you can say
I'm going to literally push to the 100%
best of my ability and those are like
either you you say I played my best and
I won or you say I put my eggs in the
basket of I wanted to win or lose like
you can't control the winning or losing
you can control going into it and giving
it your best so the same thing you can
do with any conversation is you can go
into it controlling only your end of the
deal in regardless of how much you want
to convince the other person or tell
them these magical words you think will
make them do what you want them to do or
say you never can yeah that guy can't he
can't just make you not say Jesus Christ
yeah because when you say Jesus Christ
it doesn't mean the same exact thing
that it means to him yeah he needs to
understand that exactly
unless you're Tom Brady and just the
plate the balls dude yeah then you can
win every single time yeah that's what I
would do to you
I should have deflated the ball right so
I think that maybe the ball should be a
little smart because I just bought a new
basketball yesterday and I bought 28.5
you know apparently that's a girl's eyes
but like if it feels real nice it's a
good size it's a good size I mean it's
easy keep going
sorry I didn't mean to again didn't mean
to offend the female sex about that ball
being a lot easier a little bit yeah
but what's that is uh I say that but on
a professional level those women would
kick the [__] out of me like there's no
way if I'd try to play basketball
against them again
oh very short ban but at the same time
being a man that would dunk the whole
thing about being a man or being a woman
whatever source wise it's like dude dude
do that that's the thing is i-i've never
really until all this like sexism stuff
comes along hmm
I generally I'm not kidding I don't
think I've really thought of like women
versus men in in different like women
are better at men than this or men are
better at women this make sure there's
things that are obvious that men are
just like men are just naturally
stronger like her stuff like that mm-hmm
but I'm just always like who is the best
like the best tennis player it doesn't
[__] matter if it's a girl or guy
like who's the best like who like versus
each other who is the winner who is you
know I think this that the sexism thing
like all this it's it's a word like
separation thing is something that like
another one dive into because it's very
hard conversation oh it is right now
someone someone's really if you
whoever's listening this transfer you
piss what I just said but I'm sorry no I
mean it's a it's a it's a hard come no I
mean you don't need to I don't I don't
because you didn't mean any harm just
like when you were saying Jesus Christ
yeah it's something that I agree that
should be up for conversation like if
it's like if girls are actually out here
like feeling offended by everything we
say like [__] dude let's talk
differently like let's forget wait we
can't talk to everything but know that
guys are out here like we're a couple of
good dudes mm-hmm there's nothing that
we would say that would purposely hurt
anybody like we're not trying to hurt
anyone at all yeah but but so to me I
think that like when I think of sports
or athletic ability or like who's
getting the promotion at work like who
in the Verizon company is getting the
promotion like it's the person who's the
best for the job yeah I don't care if
they have any dick her vagina I don't
care if they're freaking blind or Mew is
like dude if that guy can get it done or
that person can do a better job with you
that person deserved the job I don't
care who you are you know it's like that
I think yeah
I think the the a lot of the bakery like
that that's the thing like where a lot
of feminists and girls are probably
talking about us I have no idea but it
seems like they're probably okay cool we
get that like obviously of course but
there is a thing that we have to
actually think about and I'm sure that
there's people that are solving what we
do about this same thing with racism men
a white man our starting line of where
we were at in the beginning of time our
businesses wherever we're at like
financially sports-wise wherever we saw
our starting line is up here and women
in like so like a white male our
starting line is up here a black male is
starting lines down here mm-hmm and we
all go to the same thing women are
somewhere back here like white males
literally do have there is such thing as
privilege like yes that white privilege
like we've just had like so the years we
had a couple hundred years during
slavery where white males were like our
whole and my ancestors probably not my
actual ancestors but we're doing well
while people who I have friends who are
black or my same age their ancestors
were literally probably slaves so at the
same time where I'm a white man my
ancestors are getting better business
they're getting smarter they're whatever
they're teaching the kids this they have
this starting line where as black people
are back here women I think I'm kind of
back here with with black people so that
is something as society if that makes
any sense at all yeah that we do
probably have to I don't know figure out
something but again which they've been
trying to figure out but for some reason
someone's controlling this whole thing
to where it's still the same you know
it's like yeah they've they've gotten
pretty far with all the marches and all
the you know generate segregation and
everything else but it's still it's how
is it still here you know how is how
have we bring it back Jesus Christ Jesus
Christ yeah how are we still in the same
state that were we were in sixty years
ago you know we're like we're reverting
back to it I feel like we were out of it
and we're like cool yeah like we don't
only have segregation and they're like
and we're gonna reverse racism yeah
exactly so I don't know how that's all
working out I have not done enough
research or enough I don't have enough
knowledge to even talk about this stuff
but you see it enough and so
from media or you know well I don't know
now since I don't have social media
anymore but like at least in the news
it's like how are we still talking about
this why is this wait what is it is
still a problem yeah it's almost like
it's not a problem but they're like hey
we need to distract you or we need to
like get you guys talking about some
stupid [__] so they're just throwing it
at us man no yeah oh yeah now that makes
me want to get into like freakin
conspiracy theories like in the news and
then think about all the shootings that
have been happening again it's like man
if you need to check out that podcast
called you just call it conspiracy yeah
okay Ryan was tell me about spot casts
what was they get time over - it's
called conspiracy theories and it talks
about they have like they obviously the
normal JFK bah blah blah all that those
type of like conspiracy theories about
aliens and stuff but mostly most of the
stuff is like actually like real things
I have on the news like dipper like the
the [__] what was what was and the
shooting at the elementary that huge one
that happened like a few years ago no
Sandy Hook yeah Sandy Hook they were
talking about the conspiracy theory
about how it was your [__] you sure you
don't listen to it was pretty insane so
all that stuff like cuz I mean I like I
love me a good conspiracy theorist I
like it like che that I loved I mean to
say it's awesome it's it's you know the
funny thing is a lot of it is like it's
not trying to prove whether there is one
hundred percent across-the-board truth
or one hundred sent across the board
wrong it's kind of like hey like you can
choose to believe in these things if you
want like you can say like a that's real
like it's like it like what you're gonna
do with it like what you can do with it
like what you can say like hey man this
like Bush to 9/11 and what are you gonna
do about it though oh that's like
everyone knows I always get that you
know probably the most [__] up
situation
I know but I'm not the face didn't even
know but like I I don't know I I think
it that's just fun to bleed because you
can really toy with like man like you
know what I can't believe what I want
like I I'm gonna keep my sanity like I
you know I'm gonna like like I know
there's nothing I could do about knowing
information but like maybe there is
something I can do in my corner and you
know like like this [__] like me it's
like cool I determined like with all
these conspiracy theories like yeah it's
fun it's entertainment but I've also
determined that the government and our
political system and our society is
[__] liars like oh it's it's
dangerously liars
and so if I can have little dorky
platforms like this where I get some
smart people together to teach people
some cool stuff we can start ignoring
the news and start whatever and we start
learnings from guessing each other's
each other's intelligence rather so it
feels good to me I guess um Ryan I
definitely as much as I want to dive
down into conspiracy theories I
definitely want to talk about before we
end here okay honestly just like so I
had sent you that video I like I wanted
you on my podcast obviously I was one
like the first few people like I'm gonna
have a ton of people on there but I just
wanted you honestly was your demeanor
like you or the way that you see life
you've always been a friend of mine
that's like been so positive about
everything in your life you've also been
like I know you want a level toward to
know that you're not always positive
like you've had your ups and downs and
you've certainly gotten through them
yeah I don't I just I just think that
you are one of the most inspiring like
positive happy always smiling people
like like at your wedding I've never
seen so many teeth in my life like you
and your wife are just in your own
little world of absolute positivity like
you guys wedding eyes are just literally
just I don't know if you're just having
it like teeth comparing contents all the
time or if your should we discuss that
conscious she has better teeth and I but
but you guys just like I look over the
whole time you guys are just smiling and
laughing at all times about I don't know
if it's something in your own little
world but it's just wonderful so I I
think I don't know is there like what's
what's your perspective on life Ryan
like what are you well um I would have
to say you know I I definitely have gone
through a lot of things in my life
things that I would never wish upon
other people but at the same time I have
had a great life you know it's one of
those like you know we can talk about
depression and what I've been
through and things that have really have
taken me down till of all I never ever
want to be ever again you know but
you're you know that's just part of life
and you know I've just had a great group
of friends and had at a spectacular I
have a spectacular family that
spectacular family that have always
looked out for me you know and you know
having those experiences for you know me
you know it's trial and error and then
that that's just life you know and it's
it's whether or not you want to take
those lessons in life and like you know
this is you know the old saying I hate
it so much but I had a friend that uses
like an older friend that I used to say
this to me when I was back in high
school it's like why do we fall down why
do we fall down you know it's like so
you can pick yourself back and I hate it
you know it has worked every single time
you know it's it's whether or not you
want to get up and I do that you know
every morning I get up you know go to
work make money and go see the people
make you have the thing is you have to
make right now I suck at it but I'm
gonna get back into it again is like
right now is hanging out with you you
know you have to make the time mm-hmm
make the time out for your friends of
the people that you really enjoy your
company or the company that you enjoy
the most and that's what I feel is like
always having people with you you know
like because you don't like not seeing
like some people don't have anyone but
like for me it's like it could be like
your dog or whatever just holds like
hold onto something
hold onto something find something you
love and love oh yeah and love like find
something you love doing find someone
you love loving and let that take you
away kind of thing and that's how I've
been living my life last like probably
like 10 years maybe like I you really
find yourself I say five years last five
years that's what I've been doing cuz
you know you always going through your
20s trying to figure out who you are so
like I don't care who you a hard but
like wait it's one of those it's like
you're 25 you think you got things
figured I'm right you're like oh I
believe you
this bowl of love but now I'm 32 when
I'm 30 I thought like hey I know what's
going on these kids well but now I'm 32
and I'm still learning every single day
on the right way to love my wife the
right way to love my family it's it
never I will tell everyone it never ends
yeah and I was learning to learn as long
as you can get up every day willing to
live life Willy sometimes you gotta do
things so you don't want to do but you
do it you know that's what I've learned
definitely being with Katy like that she
does a lot of things I don't like but
you know what just go and do it and you
know what and she's she's shown me a lot
you know like I I would have to I hate
saying this because she was she was
definitely my saving grace I haven't I
had no idea what I was gonna be doing
mmm until I met her it wasn't because
like oh she saved me now she's telling
me what to do I'm like how to live life
it wasn't that it was she I found
someone just like me you know well in it
you helped you pivot it could help you
find yourself
like it once you're able to be yourself
around someone while they're being
themselves you're like now we've created
something exactly it says I think it's
like like I said you know I watched you
guys at your wedding just in your own
world we appreciate you guys being there
in freaking playing songs yeah man I'm
happy too I was happy to be part we
actually just taught me this today we
were talking about orion's coming over
and we talked about your band was so
good
a wedding is so you know what I was I
know don't know well depending on how
you want to find a DJ but yeah I mean
it's really worse but no it you know
what I would have to say this if you're
gonna have a wedding this is a site now
if you can find a good band let me tell
you it's almost inevitable it's
inevitable that jamming oh man we were
good yeah and so they've said a bunch of
cover songs they're kind of like more of
like a funky vibe like there's a even a
few songs that I actually didn't really
know but it was just everybody was going
to the vibe like I feel like once you
take away with a DJ I've noticed people
really
to control things and they think they
can were used to it we're used to being
in our cart annoying Spotify controlling
whatever yeah so at a wedding people I
can't want to hear the song I'm gonna go
tell him to play that song when it's a
band you can say I'm here at this
wedding I want to hear this song but I
don't get hear that song cool moving on
I'm just gonna dance like you just I
guess enjoy what's there rather than
trying to tribute to it exactly with a
DJ nowadays people know a little bit
about DJing now and so people think that
they should be the contributing like I
know what people want to hear right now
yeah exactly it's like everyone's a DJ
now and I don't like that I stopped but
no that ban was awesome and make sure if
you do get a band hey get a good one
like we did yeah okay good
you know oh yeah I mean we just had we
were lucky Katie's family has money
though we got a band right yeah no they
they were good they were enjoyable too
they were and I'm also like as far as
that wedding DJ this is just like a
random thought I guess you know you know
with this but I do have a DJ a couple
DJ's scheduled on the podcast right now
so we will do talk about some TJ [__] I
can talk about like why does it suck to
be a DJ at a wedding or whatever it'd be
fun right oh my god is already going
into it they shouldn't even get in a
podcast about that you guys should just
make a youtube video well I mean out
that it'll be funny well so this whole
podcast will be on YouTube anyway so I
will be so I'll be posting this on
YouTube as like different episodes
obviously it'll probably take clips so
after I have a few DJ's on here maybe I
can make one big one and make a montage
or some [__] yeah but anyway just to
route back to I think that your your
demeanor like thanks for sharing all
that I think you're right definitely
something that you've always done I have
noticed like the amount of people that I
have met through you might have cool s
people that I've met through you like
even your wedding like even like so like
Brady like I just met Brady at your
wedding yeah yeah before like just
meeting cool people through you you
attract good people and I think that
you're like the Ryan Santos you're right
Ryan Santos secret to life it's just
like
I think dude I think what you do that
you may not realize is you rip out the
good in people wherever they're at like
you you because you are so inherently
good you are so inherently and by that I
just mean like no like no no sorry I let
me explain but by that I mean you're
just so naturally nice you're so easy to
talk to so naturally your most positive
self you're so naturally like talk like
people want to talk to you I think that
you bring that up and other people like
so I've known a ton of people because of
you and I'm better for it and I think
that you like you just said a lot of
your positivity comes from surrounding
yourself with people you love but do you
also think that it's because you made
without knowing it you bring out that
love that inspiration in every person
just by being so positively yourself
because when somebody sees somebody like
like you're giving them permission to be
the most positive self so as you're
doing that like do you ever consider
that yeah I yeah sometimes I do you know
it's it's one of those how do I say I
think I took the well my dad said to me
a long time ago I think I took the same
it's too seriously sometimes but treat
people the way you should you want to be
treated you know and I I kind of I took
that really into heart because you know
like a lot of people get it sometimes
they they don't understand what they're
saying to someone definitely negative or
you because it could to to them they
could be saying like oh I did this
because out of love and it's like well
that's I don't think that you should
have gone that way or said that negative
thing about them you say I'm doing this
to like help them out and like no that's
that's I don't think that's the way you
should talk to somebody like doing
whatever you're doing but so the way I
just go about like talking to people
like people want to be listened to and
that's the hardest thing to do when
you're in a conversation is listening to
people
and you know according to Katie I still
have that problem of listening but she
doesn't know anything though okay if you
listen you don't know but I hope she
does like Katie I love you but anyways
yeah you know of a good fight later but
yeah so like what with people you don't
even know or people that I've known
forever I will sit there and listen you
know and that's half the battle is
getting to know someone without you
saying something to them because you
know like right now it's you know I love
listening to you and I don't want to say
like sometimes I'll pause or something
because I'm so interested of what you're
saying because obviously if you're this
is coming out of your head this is
coming at your from your head to your
mouth and that's out loud obviously this
is important to you mm-hmm
I because I if I want to talk to you I
want to talk to you something important
about me or I have something important
to say and I think that's where I came
like where I start understanding people
why people like you know like me in
stuff or that I'm positive always happy
because you know I never yeah you know
when I'm I'll say some stuff sometimes
just a joke around and sometimes it's
kind of a dickish thing but it's all in
play but people know that the oh you
mean oh yeah you would never mean home
yeah exactly so if I say something
something to you I want it to be like
not so much constructive or telling you
how to live your life it's it would be
like hey you know I'm just kind of
suggest suggesting something like I want
the best for you yeah and I think maybe
this would help get the best yeah and so
like you either I give them the option
to either you can listen to me or you
can do whatever you do I don't care I
just want you to be happy I don't care
if I even barely know you I just want
like I don't want the worst for anybody
right I think I don't like seeing people
sad or seeing people like get so
frustrated with life because like I've
been there you've been there kind of
thing it's like what how can we're not
helping each other out like how is this
always like a case of I'm better than
you
or we're competing like is constant
competing and I you know it's awesome to
seeing sports and stuff but like after
that games over I mean you're not the
game anymore yeah you know you're not
playing the game your game isn't
represent yeah you are you aren't that
player anymore like the games done
you're not that player anymore
you are still human so like whatever
competition just went on yeah and I
think that's just how I just go about
getting to know people or white people
think I'm smiling all the time
it's just guys I'm here to have a good
time I only only well for me I only get
this one life to live why do I don't
want to be or why do I want to be an
[__] well I don't have time for that
right you know I I just want to be happy
I want people around me to be happy and
if I can show if I can if like someone
like you notice that I I'm happy that's
awesome that makes me feel like wow like
a people someone noticed you know I I'm
living the life I want to live is being
it's like Oh Ryan so nice I'm like I
don't care it's like about that stupid
saying the nice guys finish last
I'll finish last all day every day I
don't care I just want to know about
finishing it's not about finishing last
time I'm finishing first it's like it's
not even like we're not racing friends
yes it's like just about yeah I kept
just a nice guy you can you can race oh
yeah I'm just yeah just tired all the
stress I just you know I don't want to
live not trying to be hippie-ish I guess
of living a free stress life and just
like not caring that's not what I'm
saying I'm just saying that you know
there's a lot of things to be happy
about on this in this life find it let
it take you home that's how I've been
living like that so yeah you got it
you gotta emphasize like there's always
the shitty [__] to like there's always
you know when you're living life
positively like there's always the
option for like you know there's always
a person next to you that's a don't you
see that this is terrible to you like
don't you see if I can want you mad
about this like what this is going on at
the same time that you're happy this is
going on why don't you see that but
that's just the truth of life like the
the same time that you are
Ryan Santos you're in the exact same
situation as somebody else who is so
frustrated what's the difference what
what is the difference the situation has
not changed it's the exact same
situation the Duden entity was
frustrated and your happiness frustrated
the the amount it's not about just like
pretending you're not frustrated but
it's about being able to say like okay
like I don't want to be frustrated
that's not that isn't what's best for me
yeah and then from there then you could
be like okay so how can I do it
differently and then when you go about
your day just just not concentrating on
what frustrates you are not
concentrating on the thing that's
obviously like oh this is obvious aren't
you mad about this yeah just if you just
concentrate on what's what's positive I
mean it's yeah you know you talk better
yeah if you you're gonna [__] up it's
it's inevitable you're gonna [__] up
you're gonna say things that you regret
it's whether or not you want to go back
and say hey you know either I'm gonna
make myself better this is like what I
see and I know what it takes to be
better you know or like you say some
[__] to someone that you didn't mean
dude that's okay own up do donut talked
about it yeah hey sorry you know that
hey man I kind of got mixed up in my
words I'm really sorry I didn't mean
that like due to honestly a lot of times
if you just talk to somebody man-to-man
tell him like dude I I had a friend like
that not to derail is too much but I had
a friend who I had done something that
that she didn't agree with that like
wasn't it didn't matter to her values it
was it was something essentially with
him
I didn't want to get into it it was
essentially something that she didn't
agree with but we are we're very good
friends she's a wonderful person she
considers me to be a wonderful person so
she literally came over to my house
today and said hey I won't talk to you
about this like this his father Ben
something you did and so we talked about
it and like man it just feels so much
better just like you like being able to
talk to it like it was so like I think
turnt like thank you so much for like
taking control of the situation yeah so
any any listeners if you're in a
situation where it's like you're like
cool I want to be happy like that sounds
great I'd love to be like Ryan Santos
cool Sam sounds great cool so I just
start being happy cool yeah well
man like like like what you do is
honestly these little things these
little things like that like you like
hey like this thing I don't agree with
its setup being catty about it and
texting someone and saying like hey
[__] Ryan did this thing and it
pisses me off it don't you think that
pisses you off too we should agree on
this you literally you talk to him about
it
you take the things that bother you
think things that piss you off and you
solve them dude you don't act on them
yeah I mean it could take like two or
three days who gives a [__] as long as
you find something you know yeah like
resolve something you know and not let
it just sit there cuz after that it's
like you let it fester in your in your
mind you just get more pissed about it
and then you know kind of the thing with
the whole Jesus Christ think maybe I
should you know that's one of you know
I'm kind of backtracking here but it's
like maybe I should talk to him about
that you know that's like I'm pissed
about this it's like it's actually like
it made me like kind of upset because he
got upset about it I'm like dude well
you're pissed because it's a
misrepresentation of who you know
exactly fair so maybe I should it's one
of the see it's like I'm not I'm not
perfect I'm not happy all the time yeah
you know it's you know I get frustrated
Katie gets frustrated with me all the
time oh she doesn't know what's good
yeah I know dude she's listen how we
married it if she doesn't know that it's
good you're like I don't want to crack a
joke I know but also you choose poorly
you are stuck I always do I always like
to remind Shelly like I'll do some weird
[__] like this yeah thank you that's
exactly what I do to thinking this is
what you chose like I'll just do some
embarrassing [__] yeah
and I'm whispering in your ear about
this love you can i all right Ryan well
we're getting up here fairly long for
time I feel like we should at least take
a break um if this is the end of podcast
I'll record this
Ryan Santos I love you very much thank
you for coming on to John cries I love
you a lot and I really appreciate you
for asking me to come on to this
wonderful podcast you know I thought we
were gonna run out of stuff to like talk
about because we talked earlier I said
oh god we talked about it that's what
you think but then it just goes yeah a
lot of times I'm like aha valuable to
listeners but it's like oh no it it's
like it's people like listen it's like
good people talking oh yes talking well
hopefully they don't get annoyed of my
voice if they're like oh two minutes in
I can't stand this mother for her right
now when is the last time that you
thought that when you listen to podcasts
unless it was Jim Gaffigan for some
reason the his [__] voice I don't not
a fan he's a casino comedian yeah when I
hears boy something like I can't listen
to this but otherwise everybody else I'm
cool yeah yeah I get that I like him but
like yeah I totally his voice is like
kind of whiny yeah kind of thing yeah I
know it's on what a lot of they have you
have you ever thus anybody's voice it
like like so you're saying like oh my
voice sucks I'm self-conscious about or
whatever yeah do you have you ever
actually listening you buddy like give
this [__] of my podcast oh yeah
I mean there's a few as soon as like you
just feel their voice I'm like no really
you never had that I always thought I
would have it but I'm always like I
think about it for the first 30 seconds
and I forget about it ya know there's a
there's a few that I don't like I just
like just keep listening whatever you
know yeah I just kind of you know what
this person has something of value to
say to me I just kind of have to endure
but yeah I talk about that that's why I
said that because I've heard as I was
recording something and I was talking in
the background and I heard my voice I'm
like there's no [__] way I sound like
that I'm much cooler than I
dude it's weird because it's so weird
because we think of like we hear it like
we think of all these things about
ourselves we have our voice and we're
like oh what measly I'm this I'm that
like oh I didn't rise it sound like that
but nobody thinks any of those things
they don't think about the opposite of
those things either just say that's a
voice yeah I think that's it like that's
a voice moving on yeah exactly
oh it's funny outward yeah because I
don't I guess I just know I've been
singing a lot like I've been doing more
singing I've been taking like vocal
lessons on myself and I'm like no I I'm
shaking I noticed that I'm shaking the
like self-hatred of my voice that's a
weird thing that we have like just
talking we're like yeah I sound weird
yeah I don't yeah that that's the one
thing I saw haven't gotten over is that
listening your own voice or listening to
someone else's voice that I don't really
like but I do it anyways
I don't there's something about it when
I find that voice I don't like and I'm
like what is happening why do you talk
that way it's got to be a frequency that
like we're literally like it I don't
like that frequency of your eyes okay
Ryan let's uh let's wrap it up okay Ryan
Santos I love you very much
immediately pump right here
you